Guide to the Western Pennsylvania Conservancy Records and Photographs, 1885-2006 AIS.1999.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1885-2006; 1950-2004; II.
  - Community Garden Program, 1975-2006; 1988-2004; 2.
    - PP. Homewood Gardens, Small Grants, Mrs. Savage; and Garden Tour, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Duplicate Picture Boards: North Avenue and Brighton Road; Penn Avenue and Centre Avenue; McKees Rocks; Rankin Bridge; Dormont Avenue; Mansfield Boulevard and Campbells Run Road; McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; Hazelwood; Highland Park; Allegheny River Boulevard; and South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Duplicate Picture Boards: Central, South, North, and East, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - A. 8th Avenue and High Level Bridge; and Hays, Route 885 and Glass Run Road, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - B. Aurberle Home, McKeesport; Edgewood; Hays; Hazelwood Avenue and 2nd Avenue; Mifflin School; Monroeville; Swissvale; and Westwood Elementary School, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - C. Conroy Educational Center; Hazelwood Avenue and 2nd Avenue; Homewood Montessori School; Westwood Elementary School; Edgewood; and Swissvale, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - D. Etna; and Kirkpatrick Street and Fifth Avenue, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - E. Washington Polytechnic Academy; and Canal Street and Cedar Avenue, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - F. Canal Street and Cedar Avenue; Oliver High School; Perry High School; Spring Hill Elementary School; and Thropp Way, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - G. Langley High School; McKelvy Elementary School; Oliver High School; West Liberty Middle School; Westwood Elementary School; and West End, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - H. Hazelwood Avenue and 2nd Avenue; Kirby Welcome Center I79; New Kensington; and River Trail, Northside, Mercy Foundation, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - I. Hazelwood Avenue and 2nd Avenue; Kirby Welcome Center I79; Claysville Welcome Center I70; Mifflin Triangle; and River Trail, Mercy Foundation, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - J. Penn Dot, Lawrence County; Meadville Triangle; Science Center; and Meadville 2nd School District, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - K. Fulton School; Washington Polytechnic Academy; Meadville; and Brookline Wall Project, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - L. Brookline Wall Project; Route 910 and Saxonburg Road; and New Kensington, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - M. Homestead, Moving Monument; and McIntyre Road and McKnight Road, Covering for Frost, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - N. Point State Park, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - O. Allegheny River Boulevard; Highland Park; Canal Street; and Swissvale, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - P. 8th Avenue and High Level Bridge; McKees Rocks Bridge; Saxonburg Road and Route 910; East Park; New Kensington; and Etna, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Q. Kirkpatrick Street and Fifth Avenue; Liberty Elementary School; Westwood School; and Tulips, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Q. O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street; 2nd Avenue and Hazelwood Avenue; Rankin Bridge; Tri-Boro Expressway; Uniontown; and Claysville Welcome Center, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - S. Conroy Elementary School; Langley High School; West Side Traditional Academy; and River Front Trail, River Rescue Area, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - T. Brookside Nursery, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - U. O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street; Rankin Bridge; Tri-Boro Expressway; Greenfield, Upper; and 2nd Avenue and Hazelwood Avenue, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - V. Knoxville Middle School; Langley High School; Oliver High School; West Liberty Middle School; West Side Traditional Academy; and Westwood Elementary School, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - W. Homestead; Saxonburg Road and Route 910; and Swissvale, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - X. Parkway West, Fort Pitt Tunnels and Staging Area Slope, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Y. School Garden Tour, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - Z. Brookline Wall Project, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 37)
    - Duplicates: Canna Plants; Birmingham Bridge; Linden Avenue and Thomas Boulevard; Stephen Foster; and Beechwood Boulevard and Reynolds Street, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - AA. Birmingham Bridge; Canal Street; Chestnut Street; Carnegie Science Center; Kirkpatrick Street and Fifth Avenue; McKnight Road and McIntyre Road; Mount Washington; and Spring Garden, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 39)
    - BB. Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue; Noblestown Road and Durbin Street; North Avenue and Brighton Road; Penn Avenue and Friendship Avenue; South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; Steuben Street and Middletown Road; and West End, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 40)
    - CC. Hazelwood Avenue, Beechwood Boulevard and Saline Street; Kirkpatrick Street and Fifth Avenue; Monroeville; Schenley Park Plaza; Stephen Foster; and O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 41)
    - DD. Anderson Street Bridge; Hays; Homestead; Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue; O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street; and Tri-Boro Expressway, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 42)
    - EE. Canal Street; Carson Street and Sarah Street; East Park; Mifflin School; Mifflin, Adjacent to School; and Etna, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 43)
    - FF. Brighton Road and Charles Street; Hazelwood Avenue, Saline Street, and Beechwood Boulevard; Manchester; Mansfield Boulevard and Campbells Run Road; McKees Rocks Bridge; Morrowfield Avenue, Tilbury Street, and Beechwood Boulevard; 2nd Avenue and Hazelwood Avenue; First Allegheny Presbyterian Church; and Collier Township, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 44)
    - GG. Polish Hill; and Stephen Foster, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 45)
    - HH. 8th Avenue and High Level Bridge; Meadville School; Meadville Triangle; I79, Grove City, North; and WPC Flower Planters, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 46)
    - II. Bon Air Elementary School; Langley High School; McKelvy Elementary School; Perry Traditional Academy; Regent Square Elementary School; Spring Hill Elementary School; and West Side Traditional Academy, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 47)
    - JJ. Kirby, I79, North; Latrobe, Route 30; and Uniontown, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 48)
    - KK. Latrobe, Rout 30; California Avenue and Termon Avenue; Crawford Street and Centre Avenue; McKees Rocks Bridge; Monroeville; Riverview Park; Venture Street; and Amarraca, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 49)
    - LL. California Avenue and Termon Avenue; Brookside Nursery; and Grove City, I79 South, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 50)
    - MM. Bridgeville, South, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 51)
    - NN. Etna; Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; Homestead; Linden Avenue; North Braddock Avenue and Penn Avenue; and Finance Street Community Garden, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 52)
    - OO. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds; and Hays, Route 885 and Glass Run Road, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 53)
    - PP. High Visibility Floral Beds Garden Tour, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 54)
    - QQ. East Liberty; Edgewood; Highland Park Bridge; Rankin Bridge; South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; and Swissvale, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 55)
    - RR. Allegheny River Boulevard; Crawford Street and Centre Avenue; Etna; Fifth Avenue; Highland Park Bridge; Hill District Police Station; New Kensington; Polish Hill; and Route 910 and Saxonburg Road, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 56)
    - SS. Dormont Avenue; Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue; Hill District Police Station; Grant Street; Beechwood Boulevard and Reynolds Street; Rankin Bridge; South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; Miryam's Women's Shelter; and Kirby, I79, Greene County, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 57)
    - TT. Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue; Hays, Route 885 and Glass Run Road; McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street; Swissvale; Tri-Boro Expressway; West Park Circle; and Parkway West, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 58)
    - UU. New Kensington; and Parkway West Planting, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 59)
    - VV. Spring Garden; Brighton Road and Charles Street; New Kensington Luncheon; Oliver High School; Springhill School; Washington Polytechnic Academy; and Westwood Elementary School, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 60)
    - WW. New Kensington Luncheon; East Hills Elementary School; Brashear High School; and Conroy Educational Center, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 61)
    - XX. Claysville, I70; and Indianapolis, IN., 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 62)
    - YY. Point State Park; B Street and 2nd Avenue; and Bon Air Elementary School, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 63)
    - ZZ. Longwood Gardens, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 64)
    - AAA. Garden Luncheon, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 65)
    - BBB. Meadville, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 66)
    - DDD. West End Overlook, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 67)
    - EEE. East Hills Elementary School; Brownsville, Pa.; and Moon Township, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 68)
    - FFF. Brookside Nursery, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 69)
    - GGG. Sterrett Classical Academy; Quinten Roosevelt Bulb Planting; and Homewood Montessori, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 70)
    - HHH. Perry High School; Quinten Roosevelt School; Regent Square Elementary School; Washington Polytechnic Academy; Liberty Elementary School; Bon Air Elementary School; Knoxville Middle School; Westwood Elementary School; and McKelvy Elementary School, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 71)
    - III. Parkway Planting, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 72)
    - JJJ. Parkway West Planting, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 73)
    - KKK. Parkway West Planting, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 74)
    - LLL. Ithaca, Ny.; School Garden Conference; Liberty Elementary School; Ball Seed Co,; and WPC Planters, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 75)
    - MMM. Parkway West, 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 76)
    - NN. Point State Park, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 77)
    - PP. Castle Shannon Boulevard, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 78)
    - PP. 22/30/60 Interchange, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 79)
    - XX. Brownsville, Pa., 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 80)
    - ZZ. South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 81)
    - AAA. New Kensington, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 82)
    - BBB. Morrowfield Avenue, Tilbury Street, and Beechwood Boulevard; and Hazelwood Avenue, Beechwood Boulevard, and Saline Street, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 83)
    - FFF. O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 84)
    - GGG. Hays, Glass Run Road and Route 885, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 85)
    - HHH. Stephen Foster Statue, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 86)
    - III. Hazelwood Avenue, Saline Street, Beechwood Boulevard, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 87)
    - YYYYY. Moon/Clinton; 22/30/60 Parkway Interchange; and Scott/Carnegie Interchange, 1998; Prints (Box 55, Folder 88)
    - Oil City, 1998; Prints and CD (Box 55, Folder 89)
    - Monroeville, 1998; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 55, Folder 90)
    - Mercer County, 1998; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 55, Folder 91)
    - N. Welcome Garden, 1999; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 92)
    - O. Welcome Garden, 1999; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 93)
    - Crumb Rubber Project, 2000; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 55, Folder 94)
    - Chicago, 2000; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 55, Folder 95)
    - XX. Columbus Middle School Summer Program, 2000; Prints, Negatives, Slides, and CD (Box 55, Folder 96)
    - MMM. Atlanta Children's Garden, 2000; Prints (Box 55, Folder 97)
    - AAAA. Hanging Baskets, 2000; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 98)
    - J. Liberty Elementary School, 2001; Prints (Box 55, Folder 99)
    - Y. Hazelwood Avenue, Beechwood Boulevard, and Saline Street, 2001; Prints (Box 55, Folder 100)
    - CC. Moon/Clinton, 2001; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 101)
    - HH. Brookside Gardens; and Chicago, 2001; Prints and Negatives (Box 55, Folder 102)
    - PP. Indiana, Pa., 2001; Prints (Box 55, Folder 103)
    - RR. Wylie and Elmore; and Oakmont, 2001; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 55, Folder 104)
    - A. Aviary Recap; and National Botanical Garden, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - B. East Park; Canal Street and Cedar Avenue; Stephen Foster; Schenley Park Plaza; and North Avenue and Brighton Road, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - C. Kirby; Franklin; and Waynesburg, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - D. Beaver; Brownsville; and Connellsville, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - E. Franklin; and Oil City Gateway and Fountain, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - F. Fort Pitt Elementary School, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - G. Brentwood Middle and High School; Chatham Elementary School; Fulton School Arbor Day; and Lemington Planting Day, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - I. Grove City, South; and Xeriscape Bed, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - J. Grove City, North; Xeriscape; and Franklin, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - K. Indiana, Pa.; and Franklin, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - L. Philips Elementary School; West Deer Butterfly Garden; Neighborhood Hanging Baskets; Fifth Avenue and Wyandotte Street; Belmar Elementary School; and North Murtland Street and Hermitage Street Community Vegetable Garden, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - M. Peabody High School; Philips Elementary School; and Westwood Elementary School, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - N. Brownsville; Connellsville; and Uniontown, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - O. Meadville Triangle; Moon; and Uniontown, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - P. Butler; Edgewood; Homestead; McKnight; Millvale; and Swissvale, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Q. Erie, Pa.; Meadville School; and Moon, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - R. Grove City, North; and Clarion, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - S. Beaver, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - T. Grove City, North; Kennedy Township; and South Park, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - U. Oil City Gateway and Fountain; and Franklin, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - V. Noblestown Road and Durbin Street, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - W. Kirby; and Claysville, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - X. Claysville; and Bridgeville, North, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Y. Bridgeville, South; and Waynesburg, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - AA. Point State Park; Carson Street and Sarah Street; Brentwood Middle and High School; Birmingham Bridge; Arlington Avenue and McArdle Roadway; Lemington Avenue; and Public Gardens, Nova Scotia, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - BB. Carson Street and 11th Street; Carson Street and 12th Street; Sarah Street and 12th Street; Anderson Street Bridge; and Fifth Avenue and Kirkpatrick Street, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - CC. Franklin; Grove City, South; and Bridgeville, South, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - DD. Monesson; Clairton; Weigle Hill; Wilkins Township; Etna; Haymaker; Oakmont; and Tri-Boro Expressway, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - EE. Homer Street and Walz Avenue; General Robinson Street; Scott/Carnegie Interchange; Mansfield Boulevard and Campbells Run Road; Hope Hollow Road; Lydia Street and Chestnut Street; and Liberty Tunnel, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - FF. Liberty Tunnel; Schenley Park Plaza; Weil Elementary School; Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue; and California Avenue and Termon Avenue, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - GG. Burgwin Elementary School; Forbes Avenue and South Dallas Avenue; East Liberty; South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; Hill District Police Station; Hazelwood Avenue, Beechwood Boulevard, and Saline Street; Beechwood Boulevard and Reynolds Street; and Shady Lane School, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - HH. Carson Street and Sarah Street; Spring Garden; Manchester; Penn Avenue and Friendship Avenue; and Marshall Avenue and California Avenue, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - II. Indiana, Pa., 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - KK. Chestnut Street, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - LL. East Park; Stephen Foster; and West End, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - MM. Oil City; and Franklin, 2002; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - OO. Castle Shannon Boulevard; Perrysville Avenue and Federal Street; New Kensington; and Johnstown, 2002; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - ZZ. Lincoln and Larimer; Weil Elementary School; Shaler Intermediate Academy; Crescent Early Childhood Center; Arlington Avenue and McArdle Roadway; and West Deer, 2002; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - A. Aviary Recap; and Squirrel Hill Tunnel, 2003; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - A1. Connellsville; and Franklin, 2003; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - B. Oil City Gateway; Franklin; and State College, 2003; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - C. State College; and Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - D. Meadville Gateway; Meadville School; and Franklin, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 43)
    - E. Oil City; Clarion; Grove City; and Xeriscape, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - F. Connellsville; Bridgeville; and Grove City, North, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - G. Bridgeville, South; Waynesburg; Brownsville; and Uniontown, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 46)
    - H. Scott/Carnegie Interchange; Fort Pitt Tunnel; and Squirrel Hill Tunnel, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - I. Shadeland Avenue and Schimmer Street; Marshall Avenue and California Avenue; Manchester; West Park Circle; Cedar Avenue and Canal Street; Chestnut Street; and Millvale, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 48)
    - J. Point State Park; Gateway Center, Faith's Garden; General Robinson Street; Tripoli Street; Homer Street and Walz Avenue; Spring Garden; East Park; and Oliver High School, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 49)
    - K. Aliquippa; Rochester; Mercer; and Butler Gateway, 2003; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 56, Folder 50)
    - L. Chicago, IL., 2003; Prints, Negatives, Slides and CD (Box 56, Folder 51)
    - M. Chicago, IL., 2003 (Box 56, Folder 52)
    - N. Carson Street and Sarah Street; Etna; Liberty Tunnel; and Fort Pitt Tunnel, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 53)
    - O. Oil City Gateway and Fountain, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 54)
    - P. Grant Street; 12th Street and Carson Street; 12th Street and Sarah Street; Barry Street and Josephine Avenue; Greeley Avenue and Josephine Avenue; Birmingham Bridge; and Hazelwood East, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 56, Folder 55)
    - Q. Fort Pitt Tunnel; Greengate; Mifflin Triangle; Mifflin School; 48th Street and Butler Street; Morrowfield Avenue and Tilbury Street; and Allderdice High School, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - R. Hazelwood East; 2nd Avenue and Hazelwood Avenue; Allderdice High School; South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; and Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - S. Moon; Riverview Park; Brownsville Road and Margaret Street; Brentwood Middle and High School; and South Park, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - T. Colfax Elementary School; Linden Avenue and McPherson Boulevard; Linden Avenue and Thomas Boulevard; North Avenue and Brighton Road; West Park Circle; Forbes Avenue and South Dallas Avenue; and Saxonburg Road and Route 910, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - U. Steuben Street and Middletown Road; Noblestown Road and Durbin Street; Lydia Street and Chestnut Street; Mansfield/Carnegie; Hope Hollow Road; Fort Pitt Tunnel; Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue; South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; West Deer; New Kensington; and Weigle Hill, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - V. Meadville Triangle and Meadville School, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - W. Franklin, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - X. Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; Hays; Homestead; Perrysville Avenue and Federal Street; Riverview Park; Pittsburgh Project; Science Center; and Conroy School, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Y. Meadville School; and Oil City Gateway, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Z. McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; Ivory Avenue and Evergreen Road; Beaver; and Montour Run Road, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - AA. Kirkpatrick Street and Fifth Avenue; Little Earth; Rankin Bridge; Haymaker; Haymaker Extension; and Tri-Boro Expressway, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - BB. Lemington School; Phipps Conservatory; Greentree; Mellon Bank; and Charles Street and Amanda Street, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - CC. Brownsville; Uniontown; and Connellsville, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - DD. Waynesburg; and Kirby, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - EE. Bridgeville, North; and Indiana, Pa., 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - FF. Clarion; Arlington Road and McArdle Roadway; Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue; Schenley Park Plaza; Stephen Foster; and 1835 Forbes Avenue, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - GG. Crescent School; Sarah Heinz House; Carrick; Mount Washington; Shady Lane School; and O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - HH. Highland Park; Wilkins Township; Swissvale; Edgewood; Anderson Street Bridge; Penn Avenue and Friendship Avenue; Polish Hill; Beechwood Boulevard and Reynolds Street; and 34th Street and Denny Street, 2003; Prints, Negatives, and CD (Box 57, Folder 18)